* Find Health Insurance
    * Individual & Family

Select Page

PRIVACY NOTICE
==============

Last updated January 1, 2023

#### PRIVACY NOTICE STATEMENT

We are authorized to collect personal information (PI) from you by applicable federal and state laws. Any PI we collect is used to create and manage your account, and to communicate with you about your account. PI is also used to help you apply for financial help and/or enrolling in a Marketplace qualified health plan (QHP).

If you choose to give us PI, we may share this information with Centers for Medicare and Medicaid Services (“CMS”) and will be maintained in a federal System of Records. Your PI will also be shared with other related entities. See WHEN AND WITH WHOM DO WE SHARE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?section for detail. PII is used or disclosed only for the limited purposes listed in the HOW DO WE PROCESS YOUR INFORMATION section below.

The requested PI is mandatory under the applicable laws and CMS requirements. If you chose not to provide us with the PI requested, or not to respond to certain questions, your application will be denied.

#### DEFINITIONS

As used in this privacy notice, the terms “TrueCoverage, LLC” “we,” and “us” refer to TrueCoverage, LLC, and its parents and affiliates, members, managers, officers, directors, employees, contractors, and agents. If you accept this privacy notice as an employee or representative of a company or other legal entity, the terms “you” and “your” will refer to both you, personally, and any entity you represent.

This privacy notice describes how we collect, use, protect and share information about you we obtain when you access and use our Website (defined below), including when you register for an account or request a quote. This privacy notice also applies to information we obtain when you communicate or interact with us outside of our Website, including by email, telephone, and otherwise.

Please read this privacy notice carefully before using our Website or communicating with us. Changes to this privacy notice are discussed at the end of this document.

“Users” means any individuals that access or use our website, including applicants for health insurance, insurance agents, and other registered users. References to “access” and/or “use” of our Website (and any variations thereof) include the acts of accessing or browsing our Website and accessing or using the services, information, content, features, functionality, tools, and promotions available on or through our Website.

“Website” refers to any website owned, operated, or powered by TrueCoverage, LLC (including the Website at https://www.truecoverage.com). References to our Website include any services, information, content, features, functionality, tools, and promotions available on or through each website.

BY ACCESSING OR USING OUR WEBSITE OR COMMUNICATING WITH US OUTSIDE OF OUR WEBSITE, YOU ARE ACCEPTING AND CONSENTING TO THE PRACTICES DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY NOTICE, WHICH MAY BE UPDATED AND AMENDED FROM TIME TO TIME. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY NOTICE, YOU MUST NOT ACCESS OR USE OUR WEBSITE OR OTHERWISE COMMUNICATE WITH US.

Questions or concerns? Reading this privacy notice will help you understand your privacy rights and choices. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, please do not use our Services. If you still have any questions or concerns, please contact us at Support@TrueCoverage.com.

#### SUMMARY OF KEY POINTS

This summary provides key points from our privacy notice, but you can find out more details about any of these topics by clicking the link following each key point or by using our table of contents below to find the section you are looking for. You can also click [here](https://app.termly.io/document/privacy-policy/dc1286f6-b2c1-48c4-9b42-d165f0b733a9#toc) to go directly to our table of contents.

**What PI do we process?** When you visit, use, or navigate our Services, we may process PI depending on how you interact with TrueCoverage, LLC and the Services, the choices you make, and the products and features you use. Click [here](https://app.termly.io/document/privacy-policy/dc1286f6-b2c1-48c4-9b42-d165f0b733a9#personalinfo) to learn more.

**Do we process any sensitive PI?** We may process sensitive PI when necessary with your consent or as otherwise permitted by applicable law. Click here to learn more.

**Do we receive any information from third parties?** We may receive information from public databases, marketing partners, social media platforms, and other outside sources. Click [here](https://app.termly.io/document/privacy-policy/dc1286f6-b2c1-48c4-9b42-d165f0b733a9#othersources) to learn more.

**How do we process your information?** We process your information to provide, improve, and administer our Services, communicate with you, for security and fraud prevention, and to comply with laws and regulations. We may also process your information for other purposes with your consent. We process your information only when we have a valid legal reason to do so. Click [here](https://app.termly.io/document/privacy-policy/dc1286f6-b2c1-48c4-9b42-d165f0b733a9#infouse) to learn more.

**In what situations and with which parties do we share PI?** We may share PI in specific situations and with specific third parties. Click [here](https://app.termly.io/document/privacy-policy/dc1286f6-b2c1-48c4-9b42-d165f0b733a9#whoshare) to learn more.

**How do we keep your PI safe?** We have organizational and technical processes and procedures in place to protect your PI. However, no electronic transmission over the internet or information storage technology can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, so we cannot promise or guarantee that hackers, cybercriminals, or other unauthorized third parties will not be able to defeat our security and improperly collect, access, steal, or modify your PI. Click [here](https://app.termly.io/document/privacy-policy/dc1286f6-b2c1-48c4-9b42-d165f0b733a9#infosafe) to learn more.

**What are your rights?** Depending on where you are located geographically, the applicable privacy law may mean that you have certain rights regarding your PI. Click [here](https://app.termly.io/document/privacy-policy/dc1286f6-b2c1-48c4-9b42-d165f0b733a9#privacyrights) to learn more.

**How do you exercise your rights?** The easiest way to exercise your rights is by filling out our data subject request form available here: Support@TrueCoverage.com, or by contacting us. We will consider and act upon any request in accordance with applicable data protection laws.

Want to learn more about what TrueCoverage, LLC does with any information we collect? Click [here](https://app.termly.io/document/privacy-policy/dc1286f6-b2c1-48c4-9b42-d165f0b733a9#toc) to review the notice in full.

#### TABLE OF CONTENTS

1. [WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?](#WHATINFORMATIONDOWECOLLECT)
2. [HOW DO WE PROCESS YOUR INFORMATION?](#HOW_DO_WE_PROCESS_YOUR_INFORMATION)
3. [WHEN AND WITH WHOM DO WE SHARE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?](#WHEN_AND_WITH_WHOM_DO_WE_SHARE_YOUR_PI)
4. [DO WE USE COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES?](#DO_WE_USE_COOKIES_AND_OTHER_TRACKING_TECHNOLOGIES)
5. [HOW LONG DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION?](#HOW_LONG_DO_WE_KEEP_YOUR_INFORMATION)
6. [HOW DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION SAFE?](#HOW_DO_WE_KEEP_YOUR_INFORMATION_SAFE)
7. [DO WE COLLECT INFORMATION FROM MINORS?](#DO_WE_COLLECT_INFORMATION_FROM_MINORS)
8. [WHAT ARE YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS?](#WHAT_ARE_YOUR_PRIVACY_RIGHTS)
9. [CONTROLS FOR DO-NOT-TRACK FEATURES](#CONTROLS_FOR_DO_NOT_TRACKFEATURES)
10. [DO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS HAVE SPECIFIC PRIVACY RIGHTS?](#DO_CALIFORNIA_RESIDENTS_HAVE_SPECIFIC_PRIVACY_RIGHTS)
11. [DO WE MAKE UPDATES TO THIS NOTICE?](#DO_WE_MAKE_UPDATES_TO_THIS_NOTICE)
12. [HOW CAN YOU CONTACT US ABOUT THIS NOTICE?](#HOW_CAN_YOU_CONTACT_US_ABOUT_THIS_NOTICE)
13. [HOW CAN YOU REVIEW, UPDATE, OR DELETE THE DATA WE COLLECT FROM YOU?](#HOW_CAN_YOU_REVIEW_UPDATE_OR_DELETE_THE_DATA_WE_COLLECT_FROM_YOU)

#### 1\. WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

#### PI you disclose to us

_**In Short:**_ We collect PI that you provide to us.

We collect PI that you voluntarily provide to us when you register on the Services, express an interest in obtaining information about us or our products and Services, when you participate in activities on the Services, or otherwise when you contact us.

**PI Provided by You.** The PI that we collect depends on the context of your interactions with us and the Services, the choices you make, and the products and features you use. The PI we collect may include the following:

* names
* phone numbers
* email addresses
* mailing addresses
* job titles
* usernames
* passwords
* contact preferences
* contact or authentication data
* billing addresses
* debit/credit card numbers

**Sensitive Information.** When necessary, with your consent or as otherwise permitted by applicable law, we process the following categories of sensitive information:

* social security numbers or other government identifiers

**Application Data.** If you use our application(s), we also may collect the following information if you choose to provide us with access or permission:

* _Mobile Device Access._ We may request access or permission to certain features from your mobile device, including your mobile device’s calendar, camera, contacts, microphone, reminders, SMS messages, storage, sensors, social media accounts, and other features. If you wish to change our access or permissions, you may do so in your device’s settings.
* _Mobile Device Data._ We automatically collect device information (such as your mobile device ID, model, and manufacturer), operating system, version information and system configuration information, device and application identification numbers, browser type and version, hardware model Internet service provider and/or mobile carrier, and Internet Protocol (“IP”) address (or proxy server). If you are using our application(s), we may also collect information about the phone network associated with your mobile device, your mobile device’s operating system or platform, the type of mobile device you use, your mobile device’s unique device ID, and information about the features of our application(s) you accessed.
* _Push Notifications._ We may request to send you push notifications regarding your account or certain features of the application(s). If you wish to opt out from receiving these types of communications, you may turn them off in your device’s settings.

This information is primarily needed to maintain the security and operation of our application(s), for troubleshooting, and for our internal analytics and reporting purposes.

All personal information that you provide to us must be true, complete, and accurate, and you must notify us of any changes to such personal information.

#### Information automatically collected

**_In Short:_** Some information — such as your IP address and/or browser and device characteristics — is collected automatically when you visit our Services.

We automatically collect certain information when you visit, use, or navigate the Services. This information does not reveal your specific identity (like your name or contact information) but may include device and usage information, such as your IP address, browser and device characteristics, operating system, language preferences, referring URLs, device name, country, location, information about how and when you use our Services, and other technical information. This information is primarily needed to maintain the security and operation of our Services, and for our internal analytics and reporting purposes.

Like many businesses, we also collect information through cookies and similar technologies.

The information we collect includes:

* _Log and Usage Data._ Log and usage data is service-related, diagnostic, usage, and performance information our servers automatically collect when you access or use our Services and which we record in log files. Depending on how you interact with us, this log data may include your IP address, device information, browser type, and settings and information about your activity in the Services (such as the date/time stamps associated with your usage, pages and files viewed, searches, and other actions you take such as which features you use), device event information (such as system activity, error reports sometimes called “crash dumps”, and hardware settings).
* _Device Data._ We collect device data such as information about your computer, phone, tablet, or other device you use to access the Services. Depending on the device used, this device data may include information such as your IP address (or proxy server), device and application identification numbers, location, browser type, hardware model, Internet service provider and/or mobile carrier, operating system, and system configuration information.
* _Location Data._ We collect location data such as information about your device’s location, which can be either precise or imprecise. How much information we collect depends on the type and settings of the device you use to access the Services. For example, we may use GPS and other technologies to collect geolocation data that tells us your current location (based on your IP address). You can opt out of allowing us to collect this information either by refusing access to the information or by disabling your Location setting on your device. However, if you choose to opt out, you may not be able to use certain aspects of the Services.

#### Information collected from other sources

**_In Short:_** We may collect limited data from public databases, marketing partners, and other outside sources.

In order to enhance our ability to provide relevant marketing, offers, and services to you and update our records, we may obtain information about you from other sources, such as public databases, joint marketing partners, affiliate programs, data providers, and from other third parties. This information includes mailing addresses, job titles, email addresses, phone numbers, intent data (or user behavior data), IP addresses, social media profiles, social media URLs, and custom profiles, for purposes of targeted advertising and event promotion.

#### 2\. HOW DO WE PROCESS YOUR INFORMATION?

**_In Short:_** We process your information to provide, improve, and administer our Services, communicate with you, for security and fraud prevention, and to comply with law. We may also process your information for other purposes with your consent.

**We process your PI for a variety of reasons, depending on how you interact with our Services, including:**

* **To facilitate account creation and authentication and otherwise manage user accounts.** We may process your information so you can create and log in to your account, as well as keep your account in working order.
* **To deliver and facilitate delivery of services to the user.** We may process your information to provide you with the requested service.
* **To respond to user inquiries/offer support to users.** We may process your information to respond to your inquiries and solve any potential issues you might have with the requested service.
* **To send administrative information to you.** We may process your information to send you details about our products and services, changes to our terms and policies, and other similar information.
* **To fulfill and manage your orders.** We may process your information to fulfill and manage your orders, payments, returns, and exchanges made through the Services.
* **To request feedback.** We may process your information when necessary to request feedback and to contact you about your use of our Services.
* **To send you marketing and promotional communications.** We may process the PI you send to us for our marketing purposes, if this is in accordance with your marketing preferences. You can opt out of our marketing emails at any time. For more information, see “[WHAT ARE YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS?](https://app.termly.io/document/privacy-policy/dc1286f6-b2c1-48c4-9b42-d165f0b733a9#privacyrights)” below).
* **To deliver targeted advertising to you.** We may process your information to develop and display personalized content and advertising tailored to your interests, location, and more.
* **To post testimonials.** We post testimonials on our Services that may contain PI.
* **To protect our Services.** We may process your information as part of our efforts to keep our Services safe and secure, including fraud monitoring and prevention.
* **To administer prize draws and competitions.** We may process your information to administer prize draws and competitions.
* **To evaluate and improve our Services, products, marketing, and your experience.** We may process your information when we believe it is necessary to identify usage trends, determine the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns, and to evaluate and improve our Services, products, marketing, and your experience.
* **To identify usage trends.** We may process information about how you use our Services to better understand how they are being used so we can improve them.
* **To determine the effectiveness of our marketing and promotional campaigns.** We may process your information to better understand how to provide marketing and promotional campaigns that are most relevant to you.
* **To comply with our legal obligations.** We may process your information to comply with our legal obligations, respond to legal requests, and exercise, establish, or defend our legal rights.

#### 3\. WHEN AND WITH WHOM DO WE SHARE YOUR PI?

_**In Short:**_ We may share information in specific situations described in this section and/or with the following third parties.

We may need to share your PI in the following situations:

* **Business Transfers.** We may share or transfer your information in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company.
* **When we use Google Maps Platform APIs.** We may share your information with certain Google Maps Platform APIs (e.g., Google Maps API, Places API). To find out more about Google’s Privacy Policy, please refer to this [link](https://policies.google.com/privacy). We obtain and store on your device (“cache”) your location. You may revoke your consent anytime by contacting us at the contact details provided at the end of this document.
* **Offer Wall.** Our application(s) may display a third-party hosted “offer wall.” Such an offer wall allows third-party advertisers to offer virtual currency, gifts, or other items to users in return for the acceptance and completion of an advertisement offer. Such an offer wall may appear in our application(s) and be displayed to you based on certain data, such as your geographic area or demographic information. When you click on an offer wall, you will be brought to an external website belonging to other persons and will leave our application(s). A unique identifier, such as your user ID, will be shared with the offer wall provider in order to prevent fraud and properly credit your account with the relevant reward.

#### 4\. DO WE USE COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES?  

_**In Short:**_ We may use cookies and other tracking technologies to collect and store your information.

We may use cookies and similar tracking technologies (like web beacons and pixels) to access or store information. Specific information about how we use such technologies and how you can refuse certain cookies is set out in our Cookie Notice.

#### 5\. HOW LONG DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION?  

_**In Short:**_ We keep your information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this privacy notice unless otherwise required by law.

We will only keep your personal information for as long as it is necessary for the purposes set out in this privacy notice, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law (such as tax, accounting, or other legal requirements). No purpose in this notice will require us keeping your PI for longer than the period of time in which users have an account with us.

When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your PI, we will either delete or anonymize such information, or, if this is not possible (for example, because your PI has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your PI and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible.

#### 6\. HOW DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION SAFE?

_**In Short:**_ We aim to protect your PI through a system of organizational and technical security measures.

We have implemented appropriate and reasonable technical and organizational security measures designed to protect the security of any PI we receive and process. However, despite our safeguards and efforts to secure your information, no electronic transmission over the internet or information storage technology can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, so we cannot promise or guarantee that hackers, cybercriminals, or other unauthorized third parties will not be able to defeat our security and improperly collect, access, steal, or modify your information. Although we will do our best to protect your PI, transmission of PI to and from our Services is at your own risk. You should only access the Services within a secure environment.

#### 7\. DO WE COLLECT INFORMATION FROM MINORS?

_**In Short:**_ We do not knowingly collect data from or market to children under eighteen (18) years of age.

We do not knowingly solicit data from or market to children under eighteen (18) years of age. By using the Services, you represent that you are at least 18 or that you are the parent or guardian of such a minor and consent to such minor dependent’s use of the Services. If we learn that PI from users less than eighteen (18) years of age has been collected, we will deactivate the account and take reasonable measures to promptly delete such data from our records. If you become aware of any data, we may have collected from children under age 18, please contact us at Support@TrueCoverage.com.

#### 8\. WHAT ARE YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS?

_**In Short:**_ You may review, change, or terminate your account at any time.

If you are located in the EEA or UK and you believe we are unlawfully processing your PI, you also have the right to complain to your local data protection supervisory authority. You can find their contact details here: [https://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index\_en.htm](https://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index_en.htm).

If you are located in Switzerland, the contact details for the data protection authorities are available here: [https://www.edoeb.admin.ch/edoeb/en/home.html](https://www.edoeb.admin.ch/edoeb/en/home.html).

**Withdrawing your consent:** If we are relying on your consent to process your PI, which may be express and/or implied consent depending on the applicable laws, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. You can withdraw your consent at any time by contacting us using the information in the section “[HOW CAN YOU CONTACT US ABOUT THIS NOTICE?](https://app.termly.io/document/privacy-policy/dc1286f6-b2c1-48c4-9b42-d165f0b733a9#contact)” below.

However, please note that this will not affect the lawfulness of the processing before its withdrawal nor, when applicable law allows, will it affect the processing of your PI conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.

**Opting out of marketing and promotional communications:** You can unsubscribe from our marketing and promotional communications at any time by clicking on the unsubscribe link in the emails that we send, replying “STOP” or “UNSUBSCRIBE” to the SMS messages that we send, or by contacting us using the details provided in the section “[HOW CAN YOU CONTACT US ABOUT THIS NOTICE?](https://app.termly.io/document/privacy-policy/dc1286f6-b2c1-48c4-9b42-d165f0b733a9#contact)” below. You will then be removed from the marketing lists. However, we may still communicate with you — for example, to send you service-related messages that are necessary for the administration and use of your account, to respond to service requests, or for other non-marketing purposes.

#### Account Information

If you would at any time like to review or change the information in your account or terminate your account, you can:

* Log in to your account settings and update your user account.

Upon your request to terminate your account, we will deactivate or delete your account and information from our active databases. However, we may retain some information in our files to prevent fraud, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our legal terms and/or comply with applicable legal requirements.

**Cookies and similar technologies:** Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove cookies and to reject cookies. If you choose to remove cookies or reject cookies, this could affect certain features or services of our Services. To opt out of interest-based advertising by advertisers on our Services visit [http://www.aboutads.info/choices/](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).

If you have questions or comments about your privacy rights, you may email us  
at Support@TrueCoverage.com.

#### 9\. CONTROLS FOR DO-NOT-TRACK FEATURES  

Most web browsers and some mobile operating systems and mobile applications include a Do-Not-Track (“DNT”) feature or setting you can activate to signal your privacy preference not to have data about your online browsing activities monitored and collected. At this stage no uniform technology standard for recognizing and implementing DNT signals has been finalized. As such, we do not currently respond to DNT browser signals or any other mechanism that automatically communicates your choice not to be tracked online. If a standard for online tracking is adopted that we must follow in the future, we will inform you about that practice in a revised version of this privacy notice.

#### 10\. DO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS HAVE SPECIFIC PRIVACY RIGHTS?

_**In Short:**_ Yes, if you are a resident of California, you are granted specific rights regarding access to your PI .

California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the “Shine The Light” law, permits our users who are California residents to request and obtain from us, once a year and free of charge, information about categories of PI (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared PI in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to us using the contact information provided below.

If you are under eighteen (18) years of age, reside in California, and have a registered account with Services, you have the right to request removal of unwanted data that you publicly post on the Services. To request removal of such data, please contact us using the contact information provided below and include the email address associated with your account and a statement that you reside in California. We will make sure the data is not publicly displayed on the Services, but please be aware that the data may not be completely or comprehensively removed from all our systems (e.g., backups, etc.).

#### CCPA Privacy Notice

The California Code of Regulations defines a “resident” as:

(1) every individual who is in the State of California for other than a temporary or transitory purpose and  
(2) every individual who is domiciled in the State of California who is outside the State of California for a temporary or transitory purpose

All other individuals are defined as “non-residents.”

If this definition of “resident” applies to you, we must adhere to certain rights and obligations regarding your personal information.

**What categories of PI do we collect?**

We have collected the following categories of PI in the past twelve (12) months:

|     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| **Category** | **Examples** | **Collected** |
| A. Identifiers | Contact details, such as real name, alias, postal address, telephone or mobile contact number, unique personal identifier, online identifier, IP address, email address, and account name | YES |
| B. Personal information categories listed in the California Customer Records statute | Name, contact information, education, employment, employment history, and financial information | YES |
| C. Protected classification characteristics under California or federal law | Gender and date of birth | YES |
| D. Commercial information | Transaction information, purchase history, financial details, and payment information | YES |
| E. Biometric information | Fingerprints and voiceprints | NO  |
| F. Internet or other similar network activity | Browsing history, search history, online behavior, interest data, and interactions with our and other websites, applications, systems, and advertisements | YES |
| G. Geolocation data | Device location | NO  |
| H. Audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information | Images and audio, video or call recordings created in connection with our business activities | NO  |
| I. Professional or employment-related information | Business contact details in order to provide you our Services at a business level or job title, work history, and professional qualifications if you apply for a job with us | NO  |
| J. Education Information | Student records and directory information | NO  |
| K. Inferences drawn from other personal information | Inferences drawn from any of the collected personal information listed above to create a profile or summary about, for example, an individual’s preferences and characteristics | YES |
| L. Sensitive Personal Information | Account login information, biometric data, contents of email or text messages, social security numbers, debit or credit card numbers, state id card numbers and drivers’ licenses | YES |

We will use and retain the collected PI as needed to provide the Services or for:

* Category A – 10 years as per CMS guidelines
* Category B – 10 years as per CMS guidelines
* Category C – 10 Years as per CMS guidelines
* Category D – 10 Years as per CMS guidelines
* Category F – 10 Years as per CMS guidelines
* Category K – 10 Years as per CMS guidelines
* Category L – 10 Years as per CMS guidelines

Category L information may be used, or disclosed to a service provider or contractor, for additional, specified purposes. You have the right to limit the use or disclosure of your sensitive personal information.

We may also collect other PI outside of these categories through instances where you interact with us in person, online, or by phone or mail in the context of:

* Receiving help through our customer support channels;
* Participation in customer surveys or contests; and
* Facilitation in the delivery of our Services and to respond to your inquiries.

**How do we use and share your PI ?**

More information about our data collection and sharing practices can be found in this privacy notice.

You may contact us by email at Support@TrueCoverage.com, by calling toll-free at 888-505-1815, or by referring to the contact details at the bottom of this document.

If you are using an authorized agent to exercise your right to opt out, we may deny a request if the authorized agent does not submit proof that they have been validly authorized to act on your behalf.

**Will your information be shared with anyone else?**

We may disclose your PI with our service providers pursuant to a written contract between us and each service provider. Each service provider is a for-profit entity that processes the information on our behalf, following the same strict privacy protection obligations mandated by California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (“CCPA”).

We may use your PI for our own business purposes, such as for undertaking internal research for technological development and demonstration. This is not considered to be “selling” of your PI .

TrueCoverage, LLC has not disclosed, sold, or shared any PI to third parties for a business or commercial purpose in the preceding twelve (12) months. TrueCoverage, LLC will not sell or share personal information in the future belonging to website visitors, users, and other consumers.

**Your rights with respect to your personal data**

Right to request deletion of the data — Request to delete

You can ask for the deletion of your PI. If you ask us to delete your PI, we will respect your request and delete your PI, subject to certain exceptions provided by law, such as (but not limited to) the exercise by another consumer of his or her right to free speech, our compliance requirements resulting from a legal obligation, or any processing that may be required to protect against illegal activities.

Right to be informed — Request to know

Depending on the circumstances, you have a right to know:

* Whether we collect and use your PI;
* The categories of personal information that we collect;
* The purposes for which the collected PI is used;
* Whether we sell or share PI to third parties;
* The categories of PI that we sold, shared, or disclosed for a business purpose;
* The categories of third parties to whom the PI was sold, shared, or disclosed for a business purpose;
* The business or commercial purpose for collecting, selling, or sharing PI; and
* The specific pieces of personal information we collected about you.

In accordance with applicable law, we are not obligated to provide or delete consumer information that is de-identified in response to a consumer request or to re-identify individual data to verify a consumer request.

Right to non-discrimination for the exercise of a consumer’s privacy rights

We will not discriminate against you if you exercise your privacy rights.

Right to limit use and disclosure of sensitive PI

If the business collects any of the following:

* social security information, drivers’ licenses, state ID cards, passport numbers
* account login information
* credit card numbers, financial account information, or credentials allowing access to such accounts
* precise geolocation
* racial or ethnic origin, religious or philosophical beliefs, union membership
* the contents of email and text, unless the business is the intended recipient of the communication
* genetic data, biometric data, and health data
* data concerning sexual orientation and sex life

you have the right to direct that business to limit its use of your sensitive PI to that use which is necessary to perform the Services.

Once a business receives your request, they are no longer allowed to use or disclose your sensitive PI for any other purpose unless you provide consent for the use or disclosure of sensitive PI for additional purposes.

Please note that sensitive PI that is collected or processed without the purpose of inferring characteristics about a consumer is not covered by this right, as well as the publicly available information.

To exercise your right to limit use and disclosure of sensitive PI , please email Support@TrueCoverage.com or visit: Support@TrueCoverage.com.

Verification process

Upon receiving your request, we will need to verify your identity to determine you are the same person about whom we have the information in our system. These verification efforts require us to ask you to provide information so that we can match it with information you have previously provided us. For instance, depending on the type of request you submit, we may ask you to provide certain information so that we can match the information you provide with the information we already have on file, or we may contact you through a communication method (e.g., phone or email) that you have previously provided to us. We may also use other verification methods as the circumstances dictate.

We will only use PI provided in your request to verify your identity or authority to make the request. To the extent possible, we will avoid requesting additional information from you for the purposes of verification. However, if we cannot verify your identity from the information already maintained by us, we may request that you provide additional information for the purposes of verifying your identity and for security or fraud-prevention purposes. We will delete such additionally provided information as soon as we finish verifying you.

Other privacy rights

* You may object to the processing of your personal information.
* You may request correction of your personal data if it is incorrect or no longer relevant or ask to restrict the processing of the information.
* You can designate an authorized agent to make a request under the CCPA on your behalf. We may deny a request from an authorized agent that does not submit proof that they have been validly authorized to act on your behalf in accordance with the CCPA.
* You may request to opt out from future selling or sharing of your PI to third parties. Upon receiving an opt-out request, we will act upon the request as soon as feasibly possible, but no later than fifteen (15) days from the date of the request submission.

To exercise these rights, you can contact us by email at Support@TrueCoverage.com, by calling toll-free at 888-505-1815, or by referring to the contact details at the bottom of this document. If you have a complaint about how we handle your data, we would like to hear from you.

#### 11\. DO WE MAKE UPDATES TO THIS NOTICE?

_**In Short:**_ Yes, we will update this notice as necessary to stay compliant with relevant laws.

We may update this privacy notice from time to time. The updated version will be indicated by an updated “Revised” date and the updated version will be effective as soon as it is accessible. If we make material changes to this privacy notice, we may notify you either by prominently posting a notice of such changes or by directly sending you a notification. We encourage you to review this privacy notice frequently to be informed of how we are protecting your information.

#### 12\. HOW CAN YOU CONTACT US ABOUT THIS NOTICE?

If you have questions or comments about this notice, you may email us at Support@TrueCoverage.com or by mail to:

TrueCoverage, LLC  
2400 Louisiana Blvd NE, BLDG #3  
Albuquerque, NM 87110  
United States

#### 13\. HOW CAN YOU REVIEW, UPDATE, OR DELETE THE DATA WE COLLECT FROM YOU?  

Based on the applicable laws of your country, you may have the right to request access to the PI we collect from you, change that information, or delete it. To request to review, update, or delete your PI , please visit: Support@TrueCoverage.com.

### COOKIE POLICY

**Last updated January 9, 2023**

This Cookie Policy explains how TrueCoverage, LLC (“**Company**,” “**we**,” “**us**,” and “**our**“) uses cookies and similar technologies to recognize you when you visit our website at [https://truecoverage.com](https://truecoverage.com/) (“**Website**“). It explains what these technologies are and why we use them, as well as your rights to control our use of them.

In some cases, we may use cookies to collect personal information (“PI”), or that becomes PI if we combine it with other information.

#### What are cookies?

Cookies are small data files that are placed on your computer or mobile device when you visit a website. Cookies are widely used by website owners in order to make their websites work, or to work more efficiently, as well as to provide reporting information.

Cookies set by the website owner (in this case, TrueCoverage, LLC) are called “first-party cookies.” Cookies set by parties other than the website owner are called “third-party cookies.” Third-party cookies enable third-party features or functionality to be provided on or through the website (e.g., advertising, interactive content, and analytics). The parties that set these third-party cookies can recognize your computer both when it visits the website in question and also when it visits certain other websites.

#### Why do we use cookies?

We use first- and third-party cookies for several reasons. Some cookies are required for technical reasons in order for our Website to operate, and we refer to these as “essential” or “strictly necessary” cookies. Other cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our Online Properties. Third parties serve cookies through our Website for advertising, analytics, and other purposes. This is described in more detail below.

#### How can I control cookies?

You have the right to decide whether to accept or reject cookies. You can exercise your cookie rights by setting your preferences in the Cookie Consent Manager. The Cookie Consent Manager allows you to select which categories of cookies you accept or reject. Essential cookies cannot be rejected as they are strictly necessary to provide you with services.

The Cookie Consent Manager can be found in the notification banner and on our Website. If you choose to reject cookies, you may still use our Website though your access to some functionality and areas of our Website may be restricted. You may also set or amend your web browser controls to accept or refuse cookies.

The specific types of first- and third-party cookies served through our Website and the purposes they perform are described in the table below (please note that the specific cookies served may vary depending on the specific Online Properties you visit):

#### Performance and functionality cookies:

These cookies are used to enhance the performance and functionality of our Website but are non-essential to their use. However, without these cookies, certain functionality (like videos) may become unavailable.

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | check |
| Purpose: | A simple test value used to determine if a visitor supports cookies. Set each time a visitor requests a page. |
| Provider: | truecoverage.com |
| Service: | Adobe Audience Manager [View Service Privacy Policy](https://www.adobe.com/nl/privacy.html) |
| Country: | United States |
| Type: | pixel\_tracker |
| Expires in: | session |
| Name: | ljt\_reader |
| Purpose: | Enables Lijit to recognize user browser or device when they return to their site or one of their partner’s sites. |
| Provider: | .lijit.com |
| Service: | Lijit Reader [View Service Privacy Policy](https://www.sovrn.com/privacy-policy/) |
| Country: | United States |
| Type: | server\_cookie |
| Expires in: | 11 months 30 days |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | PHPSESSID |
| Purpose: | Cookie generated by applications based on the PHP language. This is a general purpose identifier used to maintain user session variables. It is normally a random generated number, how it is used can be specific to the site, but a good example is maintaining a logged-in status for a user between pages. |
| Provider: | .www.feedspot.com |
| Service: | PHP.net [View Service Privacy Policy](https://www.php.net/privacy.php) |
| Country: | United States |
| Type: | http\_cookie |
| Expires in: | session |

#### Analytics and customization cookies:

These cookies collect information that is used either in aggregate form to help us understand how our Website is being used or how effective our marketing campaigns are, or to help us customize our Website for you.

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: |     | sd  |
| Purpose: |     | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Provider: |     | truecoverage.com |
| Service: |     | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Country: |     | United States |
| Type: |     | pixel\_tracker |
| Expires in: |     | session |
| Name: | i   |     |     |
| Purpose: | Used by Yandex Metrica for identifying site users. This cookie exists for a period of 1 year maximum. |     |     |
| Provider: | .openx.net |     |     |
| Service: | Yandex Metrica [View Service Privacy Policy](https://yandex.com/legal/privacy/) |     |     |
| Country: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |     |
| Type: | server\_cookie |     |     |
| Expires in: | 11 months 30 days |     |     |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | tap.php |     |
| Purpose: | Used to register anonymised user data, such as IP address, geographical location, visited websites, and what ads the user has clicked, with the purpose of optimising ad display based on the user’s movement on websites that use the same ad network. |     |
| Provider: | truecoverage.com |     |
| Service: | Rubicon Project [View Service Privacy Policy](https://rubiconproject.com/privacy/) |     |
| Country: | United States |     |
| Type: | pixel\_tracker |     |
| Expires in: | session |     |
| Name: |     | ab  |
| Purpose: |     | Used by Neustar to collect data on user visits to a site, such as what pages have been accessed. The registered data is used to categorise the user’s interest and demographic profiles in terms of resales for targeted marketing. |
| Provider: |     | .agkn.com |
| Service: |     | Neustar [View Service Privacy Policy](https://www.home.neustar/privacy) |
| Country: |     | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Type: |     | server\_cookie |
| Expires in: |     | 11 months 30 days |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | \_ga |     |     |
| Purpose: | It records a particular ID used to come up with data about website usage by the user. It is a HTTP cookie that expires after 2 years. |     |     |
| Provider: | .feedspot.com |     |     |
| Service: | Google Analytics [View Service Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads) |     |     |
| Country: | United States |     |     |
| Type: | http\_cookie |     |     |
| Expires in: | 1 year 11 months 29 days |     |     |
| Name: |     | xuid |
| Purpose: |     | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Provider: |     | truecoverage.com |
| Service: |     | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Country: |     | United States |
| Type: |     | pixel\_tracker |
| Expires in: |     | session |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | Pug |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Provider: | truecoverage.com |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Country: | United States |
| Type: | pixel\_tracker |
| Expires in: | session |
| Name: | 953344038/ |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Provider: | truecoverage.com |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Country: | United States |
| Type: | pixel\_tracker |
| Expires in: | session |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: |     | pxrc |
| Purpose: |     | Used to analyse how user interacts with the site to optimise ads shown to them. Expires after 2 months |
| Provider: |     | .rlcdn.com |
| Service: |     | Liveramp [View Service Privacy Policy](https://liveramp.com/service-privacy-policy/) |
| Country: |     | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Type: |     | server\_cookie |
| Expires in: |     | 1 month 29 days |
| Name: | \_ga\_# |     |
| Purpose: | Used to distinguish individual users by means of designation of a randomly generated number as client identifier, which allows calculation of visits and sessions |     |
| Provider: | .truecoverage.com |     |
| Service: | Google analytics [View Service Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads) |     |
| Country: | United States |     |
| Type: | http\_cookie |     |
| Expires in: | 1 year 11 months 29 days |     |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | audit |     |
| Purpose: | Set by Rubicon Project to record cookie consent data. |     |
| Provider: | .rubiconproject.com |     |
| Service: | Rubycon Project [View Service Privacy Policy](https://rubiconproject.com/privacy/) |     |
| Country: | Spain |     |
| Type: | server\_cookie |     |
| Expires in: | 11 months 30 days |     |
| Name: | 1026675585/ |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Provider: | truecoverage.com |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Country: | United States |
| Type: | pixel\_tracker |
| Expires in: | session |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: |     | merge |
| Purpose: |     | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Provider: |     | truecoverage.com |
| Service: |     | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Country: |     | United States |
| Type: |     | pixel\_tracker |
| Expires in: |     | session |
| Name: | \_gat |     |     |
| Purpose: | Used to monitor number of Google Analytics server requests when using Google Tag Manager |     |     |
| Provider: | .truecoverage.com |     |     |
| Service: | Google Analytics [View Service Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads) |     |     |
| Country: | United States |     |     |
| Type: | http\_cookie |     |     |
| Expires in: | 1 minute |     |     |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | \_gid |     |
| Purpose: | Keeps an entry of unique ID which is then used to come up with statistical data on website usage by visitors. It is a HTTP cookie type and expires after a browsing session. |     |
| Provider: | .truecoverage.com |     |
| Service: | Google Analytics [View Service Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads) |     |
| Country: | United States |     |
| Type: | http\_cookie |     |
| Expires in: | 23 hours 59 minutes |     |
| Name: |     | \_gat |
| Purpose: |     | Used to monitor number of Google Analytics server requests when using Google Tag Manager |
| Provider: |     | .feedspot.com |
| Service: |     | Google Analytics [View Service Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads) |
| Country: |     | Ireland |
| Type: |     | http\_cookie |
| Expires in: |     | 1 minute |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | rlas3 |     |
| Purpose: | Used to collect anonymous data related to the user’s visits to the website, such as the number of visits, average time spent on the website and what pages have been loaded, with the purpose of displaying targeted ads. |     |
| Provider: | .rlcdn.com |     |
| Service: | Rapleaf [View Service Privacy Policy](https://www.towerdata.com/company/privacy_policy) |     |
| Country: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Type: | http\_cookie |     |
| Expires in: | 11 months 30 days |     |
| Name: |     | pxrc |
| Purpose: |     | Used to analyse how user interacts with the site to optimise ads shown to them. Expires after 2 months |
| Provider: |     | .pippio.com |
| Service: |     | Liveramp [View Service Privacy Policy](https://liveramp.com/service-privacy-policy/) |
| Country: |     | United States |
| Type: |     | server\_cookie |
| Expires in: |     | 1 month 29 days |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: |     | \_\_asc |
| Purpose: |     | A cookie set by Trustpilot if you click the read more widget |
| Provider: |     | .truecoverage.com |
| Service: |     | Trustpilot |
| Country: |     | United States |
| Type: |     | http\_cookie |
| Expires in: |     | 29 minutes |
| Name: | \_ga |     |     |
| Purpose: | It records a particular ID used to come up with data about website usage by the user. It is a HTTP cookie that expires after 2 years. |     |     |
| Provider: | .truecoverage.com |     |     |
| Service: | Google Analytics [View Service Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads) |     |     |
| Country: | United States |     |     |
| Type: | http\_cookie |     |     |
| Expires in: | 1 year 11 months 29 days |     |     |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: |     | user-registering |
| Purpose: |     | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Provider: |     | truecoverage.com |
| Service: |     | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Country: |     | United States |
| Type: |     | pixel\_tracker |
| Expires in: |     | session |
| Name: | khaos |     |     |
| Purpose: | Set by Rubicon Project as an Internal user identifier used for analytics. Persistent cookie that stays for 2920 days |     |     |
| Provider: | .rubiconproject.com |     |     |
| Service: | Rubicon Project [View Service Privacy Policy](https://rubiconproject.com/privacy/) |     |     |
| Country: | Spain |     |     |
| Type: | http\_cookie |     |     |
| Expires in: | 11 months 30 days |     |     |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | \_\_auc |     |
| Purpose: | Used to track and report information to the Alexa analytics |     |
| Provider: | .truecoverage.com |     |
| Service: | Trustpilot |     |
| Country: | United States |     |
| Type: | http\_cookie |     |
| Expires in: | 1 year |     |
| Name: | ProfilesEngineServlet |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Provider: | truecoverage.com |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Country: | United States |
| Type: | pixel\_tracker |
| Expires in: | session |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | \_gid |
| Purpose: | Keeps an entry of unique ID which is then used to come up with statistical data on website usage by visitors. It is a HTTP cookie type and expires after a browsing session. |
| Provider: | .feedspot.com |
| Service: | Google Analytics [View Service Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads) |
| Country: | Germany |
| Type: | http\_cookie |
| Expires in: | 1 day |

#### Advertising cookies:

These cookies are used to make advertising messages more relevant to you. They perform functions like preventing the same ad from continuously reappearing, ensuring that ads are properly displayed for advertisers, and in some cases selecting advertisements that are based on your interests.

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | VISITOR\_INFO1\_LIVE |     |
| Purpose: | YouTube is a Google-owned platform for hosting and sharing videos. YouTube collects user data through videos embedded in websites, which is aggregated with profile data from other Google services in order to display targeted advertising to web visitors across a broad range of their own and other websites. Used by Google in combination with SID to verify Google user account and most recent login time. |     |
| Provider: | .youtube.com |     |
| Service: | YouTube [View Service Privacy Policy](https://www.youtube.com/static?template=privacy_guidelines&gl=GB) |     |
| Country: | United States |     |
| Type: | server\_cookie |     |
| Expires in: | 5 months 27 days |     |
| Name: |     | tluid |
| Purpose: |     | Set by Triplelift as a uniques user ID to collect anonymous information about the user browsing habits. Expires in 90 days. |
| Provider: |     | .3lift.com |
| Service: |     | Triplelift [View Service Privacy Policy](https://triplelift.com/privacy/) |
| Country: |     | United States |
| Type: |     | server\_cookie |
| Expires in: |     | 2 months 29 days |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | anProfile |     |
| Purpose: | Used to personalize online ads based on past actions of Datonics’ online customers. |     |
| Provider: | .pro-market.net |     |
| Service: | Datonics [View Service Privacy Policy](https://www.datonics.com/technology-privacy-policy/) |     |
| Country: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Type: | server\_cookie |     |
| Expires in: | 5 months 27 days |     |
| Name: | did |
| Purpose: | Used to show site visitors targeted ads. It expires after 2 months or 1 year. |
| Provider: | .pippio.com |
| Service: | Pippio [View Service Privacy Policy](https://pippio.com/privacy/) |
| Country: | United States |
| Type: | http\_cookie |
| Expires in: | 11 months 30 days |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | PugT |
| Purpose: | This cookie tracks when cookies were updated on the browser, in order to limit the number of calls to the server-side cookie store. Persistent cookie that expires in 30 days |
| Provider: | .pubmatic.com |
| Service: | Pubmatic [View Service Privacy Policy](https://pubmatic.com/legal/privacy-policy/) |
| Country: | United States |
| Type: | server\_cookie |
| Expires in: | 30 days |
| Name: | bkpa |
| Purpose: | Used to present the visitor with relevant content and advertisement – The service is provided by third party advertisement hubs, which facilitate real-time bidding for advertisers. |
| Provider: | .bluekai.com |
| Service: | BlueKai [View Service Privacy Policy](https://www.oracle.com/legal/privacy/marketing-cloud-data-cloud-privacy-policy.html) |
| Country: | United States |
| Type: | server\_cookie |
| Expires in: | 5 months 28 days |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | anj |     |
| Purpose: | This cookie contains data denoting whether a cookie ID is synced with an AppNexus partner |     |
| Provider: | .adnxs.com |     |
| Service: | AppNexus [View Service Privacy Policy](https://www.appnexus.com/en/company/platform-privacy-policy) |     |
| Country: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Type: | http\_cookie |     |
| Expires in: | 2 months 29 days |     |
| Name: |     | EE  |
| Purpose: |     | Used by Exelate for Target advertising. A persistent cookie that stays active for 120 days |
| Provider: |     | .exelator.com |
| Service: |     | Exelate [View Service Privacy Policy](#) |
| Country: |     | United States |
| Type: |     | http\_cookie |
| Expires in: |     | 3 months 28 days |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | YSC |     |
| Purpose: | YouTube is a Google-owned platform for hosting and sharing videos. YouTube collects user data through videos embedded in websites, which is aggregated with profile data from other Google services in order to display targeted advertising to web visitors across a broad range of their own and other websites. Used by Google in combination with SID to verify Google user account and most recent login time. |     |
| Provider: | .youtube.com |     |
| Service: | YouTube [View Service Privacy Policy](https://www.youtube.com/static?template=privacy_guidelines&gl=GB) |     |
| Country: | United States |     |
| Type: | http\_cookie |     |
| Expires in: | session |     |
| Name: |     | bku |
| Purpose: |     | This cookie is used to deliver adverts more relevant to a visitor more relevant with their interests. It is also used to limit the number of times they see an advertisement as well as help measure the effectiveness of the advertising campaign. |
| Provider: |     | .bluekai.com |
| Service: |     | Bluekai [View Service Privacy Policy](https://www.oracle.com/legal/privacy/index.html) |
| Country: |     | United States |
| Type: |     | http\_cookie |
| Expires in: |     | 5 months 28 days |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | uuid2 |     |
| Purpose: | This cookie is owned by App Nexus and used to buy, sell, and deliver online advertising, including interest-based advertising, mostly through real-time bidding. |     |
| Provider: | .adnxs.com |     |
| Service: | App Nexus [View Service Privacy Policy](https://www.appnexus.com/en/company/cookie-policy) |     |
| Country: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Type: | server\_cookie |     |
| Expires in: | 2 months 29 days |     |
| Name: |     | TapAd\_DID |
| Purpose: |     | Used to determine what type of devices (smartphones, tablets, computers, TVs etc.) is used by a user. Expires after 2 months. |
| Provider: |     | .tapad.com |
| Service: |     | Tapad [View Service Privacy Policy](https://www.tapad.com/privacy-policy) |
| Country: |     | United States |
| Type: |     | server\_cookie |
| Expires in: |     | 1 month 29 days |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | \_cc\_dc |     |     |
| Purpose: | Used by Lotame to store an indicator which tells them what data center a profile originated in (for international operations) |     |     |
| Provider: | .crwdcntrl.net |     |     |
| Service: | Lotame [View Service Privacy Policy](https://www.lotame.com/about-lotame/privacy/) |     |     |
| Country: | United States |     |     |
| Type: | http\_cookie |     |     |
| Expires in: | 8 months 26 days |     |     |
| Name: |     | IDE |
| Purpose: |     | Used to measure the conversion rate of ads presented to the user. Expires in 1.5 years. |
| Provider: |     | .doubleclick.net |
| Service: |     | DoubleClick [View Service Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy) |
| Country: |     | United States |
| Type: |     | http\_cookie |
| Expires in: |     | 1 year 11 months 29 days |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | \_gcl\_au |     |     |
| Purpose: | Used by Google AdSense for experimenting with advertisement efficiency across websites using their services. |     |     |
| Provider: | .truecoverage.com |     |     |
| Service: | AdSense [View Service Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads?hl=en) |     |     |
| Country: | United States |     |     |
| Type: | http\_cookie |     |     |
| Expires in: | 2 months 29 days |     |     |
| Name: |     | audience |
| Purpose: |     | Used to deliver targeted adverts to users based on browsing activity |
| Provider: |     | .spotxchange.com |
| Service: |     | Spotxchange [View Service Privacy Policy](https://www.spotx.tv/privacy-policy/) |
| Country: |     | United States |
| Type: |     | server\_cookie |
| Expires in: |     | 28 days |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | bcookie |
| Purpose: | Used to optimize the range of advertising on Linkedin |
| Provider: | .linkedin.com |
| Service: | Linkedin Ad Analytics [View Service Privacy Policy](https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy) |
| Country: | United States |
| Type: | http\_cookie |
| Expires in: | 11 months 30 days |
| Name: | nnls |     |
| Purpose: | Used by Liveramp for Target advertising. Persistent cookie that is saved for 60 days |     |
| Provider: | .pippio.com |     |
| Service: | Liveramp [View Service Privacy Policy](https://liveramp.com/privacy/) |     |
| Country: | United States |     |
| Type: | http\_cookie |     |
| Expires in: | 1 month 29 days |     |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | TapAd\_3WAY\_SYNCS |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Provider: | .tapad.com |
| Service: | Tapad [View Service Privacy Policy](https://www.tapad.com/privacy) |
| Country: | United States |
| Type: | server\_cookie |
| Expires in: | 1 month 29 days |
| Name: | A3  |     |
| Purpose: | Cookies set in third party websites and apps |     |
| Provider: | .yahoo.com |     |
| Service: | Yahoo [View Service Privacy Policy](https://legal.yahoo.com/ie/en/yahoo/privacy/cookies/index.html) |     |
| Country: | United States |     |
| Type: | server\_cookie |     |
| Expires in: | 1 year |     |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | didts |     |     |
| Purpose: | Used to deliver adverts that are more relevant to user’s interests. It is also used to limit the number of times a user sees an advertisement as well as help measure the effectiveness of the advertising campaign. It is valid for 2 months or 1 year. |     |     |
| Provider: | .pippio.com |     |     |
| Service: | Pippio [View Service Privacy Policy](#) |     |     |
| Country: | United States |     |     |
| Type: | http\_cookie |     |     |
| Expires in: | 11 months 30 days |     |     |
| Name: |     | test\_cookie |
| Purpose: |     | A session cookie used to check if the user’s browser supports cookies. |
| Provider: |     | .doubleclick.net |
| Service: |     | DoubleClick [View Service Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy) |
| Country: |     | United States |
| Type: |     | server\_cookie |
| Expires in: |     | 15 minutes |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: |     | \_fbp |
| Purpose: |     | Facebook tracking pixel used to identify visitors for personalized advertising. |
| Provider: |     | .truecoverage.com |
| Service: |     | Facebook [View Service Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation) |
| Country: |     | United States |
| Type: |     | http\_cookie |
| Expires in: |     | 2 months 29 days |
| Name: | lidc |     |     |
| Purpose: | These cookies are associated with a B2B marketing platform, formerly known as Bizo, which is now owned by LinkedIn, the business networking platform. This sub-domain is connected with LinkedIn’s marketing services that enable website owners to gain insight into types of users on their site based on LinkedIn profile data, to improve targeting. |     |     |
| Provider: | .linkedin.com |     |     |
| Service: | LinkedIn [View Service Privacy Policy](https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy) |     |     |
| Country: | United States |     |     |
| Type: | server\_cookie |     |     |
| Expires in: | 1 day |     |     |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | KRTBCOOKIE\_# |     |
| Purpose: | Used by Pubmatic to correlate user IDs with those of their partners (such as demand side platform clients or other advertising technology companies). Pubmatic passes the information stored by the partner in this cookie to the partner when it is considering whether to purchase advertisements. This enables the partner to make better decisions about whether to display an advertisement to a site visitor |     |
| Provider: | .pubmatic.com |     |
| Service: | Pubmatic [View Service Privacy Policy](https://pubmatic.com/legal/privacy-policy/) |     |
| Country: | United States |     |
| Type: | http\_cookie |     |
| Expires in: | 30 days |     |
| Name: |     | ga-audiences |
| Purpose: |     | Used by Google AdWords to re-engage visitors that are likely to convert to customers based on the visitor’s online behaviour across websites |
| Provider: |     | truecoverage.com |
| Service: |     | AdWords [View Service Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy) |
| Country: |     | United States |
| Type: |     | pixel\_tracker |
| Expires in: |     | session |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | \_cc\_cc |
| Purpose: | Used by Lotame to store encoded profile behaviors for interest based advertising |
| Provider: | .crwdcntrl.net |
| Service: | Lotame [View Service Privacy Policy](https://www.lotame.com/about-lotame/privacy/) |
| Country: | United States |
| Type: | server\_cookie |
| Expires in: | session |
| Name: | \_cc\_id |     |
| Purpose: | Used by Lotame to collect anonymous statistical data related to the user’s website visits |     |
| Provider: | .crwdcntrl.net |     |
| Service: | Lotame [View Service Privacy Policy](https://www.lotame.com/about-lotame/privacy/) |     |
| Country: | United States |     |
| Type: | http\_cookie |     |
| Expires in: | 8 months 26 days |     |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | TapAd\_TS |
| Purpose: | Used to determine what type of devices (smartphones, tablets, computers, TVs etc.) is used by a user. Expires after 2 months. |
| Provider: | .tapad.com |
| Service: | Tapad [View Service Privacy Policy](https://www.tapad.com/privacy-policy) |
| Country: | United States |
| Type: | http\_cookie |
| Expires in: | 1 month 29 days |

#### Unclassified cookies:  

These are cookies that have not yet been categorized. We are in the process of classifying these cookies with the help of their providers.

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | anHistory |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Provider: | .pro-market.net |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Country: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Type: | server\_cookie |
| Expires in: | 30 days |
| Name: | u   |     |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Provider: | .agkn.com |     |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Country: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Type: | server\_cookie |     |
| Expires in: | 11 months 30 days |     |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | IQver |     |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Provider: | .intentiq.com |     |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Country: | United States |     |
| Type: | http\_cookie |     |
| Expires in: | 1 year 11 months 29 days |     |
| Name: | rl\_visitor\_history |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Provider: | truecoverage.com |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Country: | United States |
| Type: | http\_cookie |
| Expires in: | session |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | capture\_base\_site\_id |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Provider: | truecoverage.com |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Country: | United States |
| Type: | html\_local\_storage |
| Expires in: | persistent |
| Name: | b9ef63b3-795a-4e39-b47d-b785d2427173\_bot\_type |     |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Provider: | truecoverage.com |     |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Country: | United States |     |
| Type: | html\_local\_storage |     |
| Expires in: | persistent |     |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | intentIQCDate |     |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Provider: | .intentiq.com |     |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Country: | United States |     |
| Type: | server\_cookie |     |
| Expires in: | 1 year 11 months 29 days |     |
| Name: | \_\_io\_cid |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Provider: | .bfmio.com |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Country: | United States |
| Type: | http\_cookie |
| Expires in: | 11 months 29 days |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | suid |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Provider: | .simpli.fi |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Country: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Type: | http\_cookie |
| Expires in: | 1 year |
| Name: | b9ef63b3-795a-4e39-b47d-b785d2427173\_rl\_campaign |     |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Provider: | truecoverage.com |     |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Country: | United States |     |
| Type: | html\_session\_storage |     |
| Expires in: | session |     |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | prism\_253918769 |     |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Provider: | prism.app-us1.com |     |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Country: | United States |     |
| Type: | server\_cookie |     |
| Expires in: | 30 days |     |
| Name: | uid\_syncd\_secure |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Provider: | .simpli.fi |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Country: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Type: | server\_cookie |
| Expires in: | 7 days |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | sifi\_user\_id |     |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Provider: | b9ef63b3-795a-4e39-b47d-b785d2427173.rlets.com |     |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Country: | United States |     |
| Type: | http\_cookie |     |
| Expires in: | 9 years 11 months 28 days |     |
| Name: | sifi\_user\_id |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Provider: | truecoverage.com |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Country: | United States |
| Type: | http\_cookie |
| Expires in: | session |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | lang |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Provider: | .ads.linkedin.com |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Country: | United States |
| Type: | http\_cookie |
| Expires in: | session |
| Name: | fs\_ref\_ |     |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Provider: | www.feedspot.com |     |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Country: | United States |     |
| Type: | server\_cookie |     |
| Expires in: | 30 days |     |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | \_ljtrtb\_2 |     |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Provider: | .lijit.com |     |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Country: | United States |     |
| Type: | http\_cookie |     |
| Expires in: | 11 months 30 days |     |
| Name: | li\_sugr |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Provider: | .linkedin.com |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Country: | United States |
| Type: | http\_cookie |
| Expires in: | 2 months 29 days |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | b9ef63b3-795a-4e39-b47d-b785d2427173\_visitor\_id |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Provider: | truecoverage.com |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Country: | United States |
| Type: | html\_local\_storage |
| Expires in: | persistent |
| Name: | b9ef63b3-795a-4e39-b47d-b785d2427173\_override\_site\_id |     |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Provider: | truecoverage.com |     |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Country: | United States |     |
| Type: | html\_local\_storage |     |
| Expires in: | persistent |     |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | b9ef63b3-795a-4e39-b47d-b785d2427173\_last\_activity\_at |     |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Provider: | truecoverage.com |     |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Country: | United States |     |
| Type: | html\_local\_storage |     |
| Expires in: | persistent |     |
| Name: | rl\_initial\_referrer |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Provider: | truecoverage.com |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Country: | United States |
| Type: | html\_local\_storage |
| Expires in: | persistent |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | b9ef63b3-795a-4e39-b47d-b785d2427173\_history\_referrer\_type |     |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Provider: | truecoverage.com |     |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Country: | United States |     |
| Type: | html\_local\_storage |     |
| Expires in: | persistent |     |
| Name: | ud  |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Provider: | .exelator.com |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Country: | United States |
| Type: | server\_cookie |
| Expires in: | 3 months 28 days |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | fs\_ref\_ |     |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Provider: | widgets.feedspot.com |     |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Country: | United States |     |
| Type: | server\_cookie |     |
| Expires in: | 30 days |     |
| Name: | UID |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Provider: | .ads.stickyadstv.com |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Country: | United States |
| Type: | http\_cookie |
| Expires in: | 30 days |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | ASPNETSessionId\_BE |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Provider: | shop.truecoverage.com |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Country: | United States |
| Type: | http\_cookie |
| Expires in: | session |
| Name: | rl\_last\_known\_activity\_at |     |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Provider: | truecoverage.com |     |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Country: | United States |     |
| Type: | html\_local\_storage |     |
| Expires in: | persistent |     |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | RLEU |     |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Provider: | truecoverage.com |     |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Country: | United States |     |
| Type: | html\_session\_storage |     |
| Expires in: | session |     |
| Name: | rl\_os |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Provider: | truecoverage.com |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Country: | United States |
| Type: | html\_local\_storage |
| Expires in: | persistent |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | b9ef63b3-795a-4e39-b47d-b785d2427173\_sifi\_user\_id |     |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Provider: | truecoverage.com |     |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Country: | United States |     |
| Type: | html\_local\_storage |     |
| Expires in: | persistent |     |
| Name: | \_\_141\_cid |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Provider: | .bfmio.com |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Country: | United States |
| Type: | server\_cookie |
| Expires in: | 11 months 30 days |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | uid\_syncd |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Provider: | .simpli.fi |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Country: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Type: | http\_cookie |
| Expires in: | 7 days |
| Name: | rl\_initial\_page\_uri |     |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Provider: | truecoverage.com |     |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Country: | United States |     |
| Type: | html\_local\_storage |     |
| Expires in: | persistent |     |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | uid-bp-# |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Provider: | .ads.stickyadstv.com |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Country: | United States |
| Type: | server\_cookie |
| Expires in: | 1 day |
| Name: | visitor\_id |     |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Provider: | b9ef63b3-795a-4e39-b47d-b785d2427173.rlets.com |     |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Country: | United States |     |
| Type: | server\_cookie |     |
| Expires in: | 10 years |     |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | suid\_legacy |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Provider: | .simpli.fi |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Country: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Type: | server\_cookie |
| Expires in: | 1 year |
| Name: | RlocalSessionOptOut |     |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Provider: | truecoverage.com |     |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Country: | United States |     |
| Type: | html\_session\_storage |     |
| Expires in: | session |     |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | b9ef63b3-795a-4e39-b47d-b785d2427173\_history\_campaign |     |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Provider: | truecoverage.com |     |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Country: | United States |     |
| Type: | html\_local\_storage |     |
| Expires in: | persistent |     |
| Name: | test |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Provider: | b9ef63b3-795a-4e39-b47d-b785d2427173.rlets.com |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Country: | United States |
| Type: | http\_cookie |
| Expires in: | 1 day |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | intentIQ |     |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Provider: | .intentiq.com |     |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Country: | United States |     |
| Type: | server\_cookie |     |
| Expires in: | 1 year 11 months 29 days |     |
| Name: | IDSYNC |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Provider: | .analytics.yahoo.com |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Country: | United States |
| Type: | http\_cookie |
| Expires in: | 11 months 30 days |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | prism\_253918769 |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Provider: | .truecoverage.com |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Country: | United States |
| Type: | http\_cookie |
| Expires in: | 29 days |
| Name: | \_monsterinsights\_uj |     |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Provider: | truecoverage.com |     |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |     |
| Country: | United States |     |
| Type: | http\_cookie |     |
| Expires in: | 11 months 30 days |     |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Name: | b9ef63b3-795a-4e39-b47d-b785d2427173\_visit\_id |
| Purpose: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Provider: | truecoverage.com |
| Service: | \_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_ |
| Country: | United States |
| Type: | html\_local\_storage |
| Expires in: | persistent |

#### How can I control cookies on my browser?

As the means by which you can refuse cookies through your web browser controls vary from browser to browser, you should visit your browser’s help menu for more information. The following is information about how to manage cookies on the most popular browsers:

In addition, most advertising networks offer you a way to opt out of targeted advertising. If you would like to find out more information, please visit:

#### What about other tracking technologies, like web beacons?

Cookies are not the only way to recognize or track visitors to a website. We may use other, similar technologies from time to time, like web beacons (sometimes called “tracking pixels” or “clear gifs”). These are tiny graphics files that contain a unique identifier that enables us to recognize when someone has visited our Website or opened an email including them. This allows us, for example, to monitor the traffic patterns of users from one page within a website to another, to deliver or communicate with cookies, to understand whether you have come to the website from an online advertisement displayed on a third-party website, to improve site performance, and to measure the success of email marketing campaigns. In many instances, these technologies are reliant on cookies to function properly, and so declining cookies will impair their functioning.

#### Do you use Flash cookies or Local Shared Objects?

Websites may also use so-called “Flash Cookies” (also known as Local Shared Objects or “LSOs”) to, among other things, collect and store information about your use of our services, fraud prevention, and for other site operations.

If you do not want Flash Cookies stored on your computer, you can adjust the settings of your Flash player to block Flash Cookies storage using the tools contained in the [Website Storage Settings Panel](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html#_blank). You can also control Flash Cookies by going to the [Global Storage Settings Panel](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager03.html#_blank) and following the instructions (which may include instructions that explain, for example, how to delete existing Flash Cookies (referred to “information” on the Macromedia site), how to prevent Flash LSOs from being placed on your computer without your being asked, and (for Flash Player 8 and later) how to block Flash Cookies that are not being delivered by the operator of the page you are on at the time).

Please note that setting the Flash Player to restrict or limit acceptance of Flash Cookies may reduce or impede the functionality of some Flash applications, including, potentially, Flash applications used in connection with our services or online content.

#### Do you serve targeted advertising?  

Third parties may serve cookies on your computer or mobile device to serve advertising through our Website. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide relevant advertisements about goods and services that you may be interested in. They may also employ technology that is used to measure the effectiveness of advertisements. They can accomplish this by using cookies or web beacons to collect information about your visits to this and other sites in order to provide relevant advertisements about goods and services of potential interest to you. The information collected through this process does not enable us or them to identify your name, contact details, or other details that directly identify you unless you choose to provide these.

#### How often will you update this Cookie Policy?  

We may update this Cookie Policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to the cookies we use or for other operational, legal, or regulatory reasons. Please, therefore, re-visit this Cookie Policy regularly to stay informed about our use of cookies and related technologies.

The date at the top of this Cookie Policy indicates when it was last updated.

#### Where can I get further information?  

If you have any questions about our use of cookies or other technologies, please email us at paul.montgomery@truecoverage.com or by mail to:

TrueCoverage, LLC  
2400 Louisiana Blvd NE, BLDG #3  
Albuquerque, NM 87110  
United States  
Phone: (+1)888-505-1815

**Media Inquiries:**  
Catherine Riedel  
Next Level Everything  

[

](https://truecoverage.com/accessibility-statement/)[

](https://www.bbb.org/us/nm/albuquerque/profile/health-insurance/truecoverage-llc-0806-99160073/accreditation-information)

By using this site, you consent and request to be contacted by TrueCoverage, their agents, affiliates, or anyone calling on our behalf, by phone, email, and text/SMS to the home or mobile number(s) you provided, even if your provided number is on a National, State, or Private, Do Not Call List. Expect pre-recorded messages and automated technology to be used to contact you for marketing purposes. You understand that consent is not a condition of purchase.

CLOSE

* Name
    
     First Last
    
* Agency Name
    
* State\*
    
    StateAlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareFloridaGeorgiaHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyoming
    
* Phone
    
* Email
    
* What business you are interested\*
    
    *  Health
    *  Medicare
    *  Life
    *  Ancillary
    *  Others
    
* Best time to contact\*
    
    *  9-12 EST
    *  2-6 PM EST
    
* Message\*
    
* CAPTCHA
    
* By clicking SUBMIT, you consent and request to be contacted by TrueCoverage and their licensed agents, by phone, email, and text/SMS to the home or mobile number(s) you provided, even if your provided number is on a National, State or Private Do Not Call List. In some cases, pre-recorded messages and automated technology may be used to contact you for marketing purposes. I understand that consent is not a condition of purchase.
    
    * [ ]  By clicking SUBMIT, you consent and request to be contacted by TrueCoverage and their licensed agents, by phone, email, and text/SMS to the home or mobile number(s) you provided, even if your provided number is on a National, State or Private Do Not Call List. In some cases, pre-recorded messages and automated technology may be used to contact you for marketing purposes. I understand that consent is not a condition of purchase.
    
* 
* Hidden
    
    GCLID field
    
* 
    
* Comments
    
    This field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.

**TCPA Consent:**  
By clicking SUBMIT, you consent and request to be contacted by TrueCoverage, their agents, affiliates, or anyone calling on our behalf by phone, email, and text/SMS to the home or mobile number(s) you provided, even if your provided number is on a National, State, or Private, Do Not Call List. Expect pre-recorded messages and automated technology to contact you for marketing purposes. You understand that consent is not a condition of purchase.

Δ

×

#### Choose the Types of Insurance that you’d like information about:

Select Insurance(Required)

 Health Insurance

 Medicare Options

 Vision Insurance

 Life Insurance

 Dental Insurance

 Other

 Small Business Insurance

#### Health Insurance - a Quick Message:

If you’re looking for Health Insurance right now, we will search the subsidized Marketplace (Affordable Care Act / Obamacare / Bidencare) for plans that meet your needs. More than 70% of clients qualify to get this insurance for $0.

If you have Health Insurance right now, we can arrange to find you a better plan during the next Open Enrollment period (November 1st, 2021 – December 15th, 2021).

Complete the form below, and we’ll reach out to assist you!

Great and VERY Low-cost, _or FREE_ $0, Health Insurance, and More!
------------------------------------------------------------------

* * *

First Name(Required)

Last Name(Required)

Email(Required)

Phone(Required)

Address(Required)

City(Required)

State(Required)

Zip Code(Required)

Birthdate

Month123456789101112

Day12345678910111213141516171819202122232425262728293031

Year2025202420232022202120202019201820172016201520142013201220112010200920082007200620052004200320022001200019991998199719961995199419931992199119901989198819871986198519841983198219811980197919781977197619751974197319721971197019691968196719661965196419631962196119601959195819571956195519541953195219511950194919481947194619451944194319421941194019391938193719361935193419331932193119301929192819271926192519241923192219211920

Hidden

GCLID field

Date

 MM slash DD slash YYYY

CAPTCHA

**TCPA Consent:**  
By clicking SUBMIT, you consent and request to be contacted by TrueCoverage, their agents, affiliates, or anyone calling on our behalf by phone, email, and text/SMS to the home or mobile number(s) you provided, even if your provided number is on a National, State, or Private, Do Not Call List. Expect pre-recorded messages and automated technology to contact you for marketing purposes. You understand that consent is not a condition of purchase.

Δ

×

[

](https://www.monsterinsights.com/?utm_source=verifiedBadge&utm_medium=verifiedBadge&utm_campaign=verifiedbyMonsterInsights)
